<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string-array name="article_titles">
        <item>Wild Stack Frenzy</item>
        <item>Coin Win: Hold The Spin</item>
        <item>Mammoth Tundra</item>
        <item>Wizard Blizzard x5</item>
        <item>Power of The Vikings</item>
        <item>Epic Fire 40</item>
        <item>Candy Blitz</item>
        <item>Kraken\'s Sky Bounty</item>
        <item>Big Bass Amazon Xtreme</item>
        <item>Bamboo Wilds</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="article_content">
        <item>Wild Stack Frenzy invites us to dig down into the earth and awaken the adventurer in
            us. What can you find there? You’ll never know! You might come across various remains
            of prehistoric creatures or endless treasures to dig out. See what the cave of
            Wild Stack Frenzy offers in this Wild Stack Frenzy slot review.
            \n
            Judging from the slot’s title, we can expect to see the Wild Stack feature as the main
            offer of the game. The Wild Frenzy slot machine design perfectly matches
            the distinctive theme, too.
        </item>
        <item>Gamzix adds to its collection of online video slots with the Hold The Spin feature
            with this release. The Coin Win: Hold The Spin game has a unique cross-shaped grid that
            caught our attention. Our interest further deepened when we discovered it has four
            jackpots.
            \n
            In this Coin Win: Hold The Spin slot review, we’ll share our experience on this
            one-of-a-kind game. We’ll tell you about the main game and bonus features. We also
            mention where you can enjoy playing it in real money mode. Read on to find out what
            triggers the jackpots in this slot.
        </item>
        <item>Rarely do we see the Ice Age and its fauna as the subject for a slot, but
            Booming Games did just that with the Mammoth Tundra slot machine. The glacial period,
            when mammoths roamed and ruled the continents, comes to life in Mammoth Tundra.
            Snow and ice don\'t often make for pleasant scenes since they make you feel chilly,
            but if you\'re fortunate enough to win some huge rewards, you\'ll undoubtedly feel
            warm and fuzzy.
            \n
            The excitement hides in the Free Spins rounds, where the high-paying (major) symbols
            can upgrade. There are also expanding Wilds to look forward to. Join us as we venture
            into the cold to discover what this game offers in our Mammoth Tundra slot review.
        </item>
        <item>If you’re wondering how it feels to enter a magical forest, Wizard Blizzard x5
            invites you to experience the enchanted thicket. You’ll find all sorts of magical
            creatures and items, or you might encounter the sorceress and sorcerer while you
            wander around. Let’s explore deeper into the mysterious forest through our Wizard
            Blizzard x5 slot review!
            \n
            Wizard Blizzard x5 gives a nod to classic slot design, where the background isn’t
            as clearly drawn as what we often find in modern online slots. However,
            Wizard Blizzard x5 has multiple exciting features that make our trip through
            the magical world even more thrilling.
            \n
            The game has a Free Spins feature, but the Wild played a big part in our trial run
            and helped give us multiple wins.
        </item>
        <item>Many online slots players love Viking-themed games. Power of the Vikings follows
            axe-wielding soldiers conquering territory and pillaging villages. If this is your
            vibe, you’ll enjoy this action in the Power of The Vikings game. It also has
            high-quality graphics and cool features for an immersive experience.
            \n
            We’ll tell you how to navigate this quest in this Power of The Vikings slot review.
            We’ll look at the main game and bonus features. We’ll also mention the best online
            casino sites where you can join the Vikings on your quest for big payouts.
        </item>
        <item>Our Epic Fire 40 slot review is more than just testing out the game. It involves
            answering the question, can traditional slots and video slots mix? This game has many
            classic elements, such as bar and fruit symbols and Scatters that pay out anywhere
            but don’t lead to a bonus round.
            \n
            In our online slot reviews, we highlight the immersive nature of a slot. However,
            when the theme doesn’t come together, and there’s no narrative, then we have to look
            at other aspects for entertainment. That’s the case here, as fruit and fire themes
            don’t really connect.
            \n
            On the other hand, the Epic Fire 40 real money slot has plenty of paylines, fiery
            animations, Wild symbols and random jackpot wins. All of these stop the game from
            being ordinary and give it a certain appeal.
        </item>
        <item>Pragmatic Play has dropped some of the best sweet-themed slots in the market,
            and they’re back with another one. This digital Candy Blitz slot machine has a fun
            mechanic that features a pay-anywhere system. That means instead of traditional slot
            paylines, you’ll land a win if eight or more of the same symbols are present anywhere
            on the reels.
            \n
            The tumbling reels ensure you can land more possible wins during your spin, sometimes
            working well with the pay-anywhere mechanic to eliminate more than half the symbols
            on the reels. The characters are all delicious-looking sweets.
            \n
            On the left of the reels, you’ll also see a small screen that shows you the wins you
            land within a single spin. You can place bets as low as £0.20 per spin, perfect for
            casual players. However, high-rollers aren’t left out, as the maximum bet is £240.
            This slot has six reels and five rows in which multiple symbols can fall.
        </item>
        <item>This slot is set on a wooden pirate ship with cannons shooting in the clouds. On the
            deck, you can see Kraken wiggling below the play grid. The wood-framed grid sits
            imposingly in the middle of the game screen and is dotted with pirate-themed symbols.
            \n
            As seen in the theme and graphics, Pragmatic Play outdid itself in making this game.
            The sea shanty blasting as you play this slot reiterates the attention to detail.
            It’s only interrupted by high-pitched sounds of falling symbols and Kraken’s evil
            laugh when a Wild lands on the grid.
            \n
            Like most pirate-themed video slots, this slot features symbols such as a ship wheel
            and swords on the grid. Instead of regular playing cards, this slot features gemstones
            among its symbols, adding colour to the grid.
            \n
            Typical of this provider, the game’s interface and background music match in perfect
            harmony to create an immersive play atmosphere.
        </item>
        <item>Pragmatic Play and its partner, Reel Kingdom, created a new title in
            the Big Bass Slot series. The design of this game follows the standard 5 reel slot,
            three-row layout. As for the slot paylines, there are 10 and they’re fixed.
            The paytable’s highest payout is 200x your stake, the iconic bass is your Scatter,
            while the fisherman is your Wild.
            \n
            Like the previous iterations, it boasts immersive gameplay where you join the fisherman
            on his trip to the Amazon River to catch new and exciting fish species. With a scenic
            Amazon river view making up the background, you have much to look forward to when you
            play this slot.
            \n
            With the fisherman sitting in his boat at the top of the reels, the rest of the reels
            show an underwater scene, with colourful fish as the money symbols. The standard
            symbols are fishing gear like his backpack and fishing rod, and a toucan and card faces
            10, J, Q, K, and A.
            \n
            Like most Pragmatic Play slots, the soundtrack boasts sounds you’d find in the jungle,
            like animal chatter, along with a cheerful tune to set the ambience. You have settings
            where you can remove the ambient music or the sound effects, and choose between Battery
            Saver mode and Quick Spin mode.
        </item>
        <item>Booming Games is the game provider of the Bamboo Wilds slot demo and real money slots
            title. The Asian-themed higher paying slot’s symbols range from a golden Buddha, a
            lucky cat, and a pot of gold to golden coins, a lucky charm, and the New Year’s red
            envelope.
            \n
            The lower paying symbols are 10, J, Q, K, and A, while the Scatter is the golden panda,
            and the Wild is the yin-yang symbol, with a multiplier on top. Traditional Asian
            architecture, which follows the design of a shrine/temple, surrounds these symbols.
            \n
            The sound is a cheerful Asian tune, immersing you into the culture and theme of the
            slot. Overall, this slot delivers a detailed design yet remains slightly different from
            other Asian-themed slots. The quality graphics and sound ensures you will enjoy
            spinning the reels.
            \n
            There are 20 fixed paylines, and the settings allow you to change the slot gameplay
            to fit you better.
        </item>
    </string-array>
</resources>