<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Fair Go Casino Review</string>
    <string name="loading">Loading…</string>
    <string name="home">Home</string>
    <string name="privacy">Privacy</string>
    <string name="privacy_policy">Privacy Policy</string>
    <string name="privacy_policy_text">Fair Go Casino Review mobile application (App) is provided by
        at no cost and is intended for use as is.
        \n
        This page is used to inform visitors regarding Apps policies with the collection, use, and
        disclosure of Personal Information if anyone decided to use App.
        \n
        If you choose to use App, then you agree to the collection and use of information in
        relation to this policy. The Personal Information that Fair Go Casino Review app collect is
        used for providing and improving the App. This app will not use or share your information
        with anyone except as described in this Privacy Policy.
        \n
        The terms used in this Privacy Policy have the same meanings as in our Terms and Conditions,
        which are accessible at Fair Go Casino Review unless otherwise defined in this
        Privacy Policy.
        \n
        Information Collection and Use
        \n
        For a better experience, while using our App, it may require you to provide us with certain
        personally identifiable information, including but not limited to device id. The app does
        use services that may collect information used to identify you.
        \n
        Google Services
        \n
        Firebase Analytics
        \n
        Log Data
        \n
        App informs you that whenever you use it, in a case of an error in the app App collects data
        and information (through third-party products) on your phone called Log Data. This Log Data
        may include information such as your device Internet Protocol (“IP”) address, device name,
        operating system version, the configuration of the app when utilizing App, the time and date
        of your use of App, and other statistics.
        \n
        Cookies
        \n
        Cookies are files with a small amount of data that are commonly used as anonymous unique
        identifiers. These are sent to your browser from the websites that you visit and are stored
        on your device\'s internal memory.
        \n
        This App does not use these “cookies” explicitly. However, the app may use third-party code
        and libraries that use “cookies” to collect information and improve their services. You have
        the option to either accept or refuse these cookies and know when a cookie is being sent to
        your device. If you choose to refuse our cookies, you may not be able to use some portions
        of this App.
        \n
        Service Providers
        \n
        App may employ third-party companies and individuals due to the following reasons:
        \n
        To facilitate our App;
        \n
        To provide the Service on our behalf;
        \n
        To perform Service-related services; or
        \n
        To assist us in analyzing how our App is used.
        \n
        App informs users that these third parties have access to their Personal Information.
        The reason is to perform the tasks assigned to them on our behalf. However, they are
        obligated not to disclose or use the information for any other purpose.
        \n
        Security
        \n
        App values your trust in providing us your Personal Information, thus we are striving to
        use commercially acceptable means of protecting it. But remember that no method of
        transmission over the internet, or method of electronic storage is completely secure and
        reliable, and App cannot guarantee its absolute security.
        \n
        Links to Other Sites
        \n
        This App may contain links to other sites. If you click on a third-party link, you will be
        directed to that site. Note that these external sites are not operated by app. Therefore,
        App strongly advise you to review the Privacy Policy of these websites. App have no control
        over and assume no responsibility for the content, privacy policies, or practices of any
        third-party sites or services.
        \n
        Children’s Privacy
        \n
        This App does not address anyone under the age of 18. App does not knowingly collect
        personally identifiable information from children under 18 years of age. In the case App
        discovers that a child under 18 has provided  personal information, App immediately delete
        this from servers. If you are a parent or guardian and you are aware that your child has
        provided us with personal information, please contact us so that we will be able to do
        the necessary actions.
        \n
        Changes to This Privacy Policy
        \n
        We may update our Privacy Policy from time to time. Thus, you are advised to review this
        page periodically for any changes. We will notify you of any changes by posting
        the new Privacy Policy on this page.
        \n
        \n
        Contact Us
        \n
        If you have any questions or suggestions about Privacy Policy, do not hesitate to contact
        us at <a>flutterhassan999@gmail.com</a>.
    </string>
    <string name="article_image">Article image</string>
    <string name="go_back">Go back</string>
</resources>